<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 02:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2014 02:27:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gerrogate</title>
      <link>//gerrogate.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>//gerrogate</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With my morning brew in hand I checked my emails before anything else, a decision that started my day the wrong way…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“An email from Andrew McQuaid?”, I muttered mid-brew and half-asleep. “Sent at 2:20am? That’s a Euromail.” Despite the dots, my under-caffeinated mind wasn’t prepared for the content of this email title “Mr Simon Gerrans”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“A Cease &amp;amp; Desist letter? What the fuck? I need another brew.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confused by the vagueness and bemused by the poor punctuation, I read this legal letter again, twice. There was no confusing the complaint —it referred to a blurb I wrote just weeks ago— but there was much confusing the claim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I refer you to […] the line &lt;em&gt;“Sock Height is launching this July like Gerro on a Belgium berg.”&lt;/em&gt; This reference to “Gerro” infringes Mr Gerran’s intellectual property.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Wow”, I said while yummying down on my second Scotch Finger of the day, “Are they taking the piss? Because they couldn’t be more wrong: that is not &lt;em&gt;a line&lt;/em&gt;… that is &lt;em&gt;blurb art&lt;/em&gt;. And if they think I’m just going to sit here and let them belittle my work, they can goooo…..”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, I don’t care about Andrew. I was up on some cycling forums today, there was a kid couldn’t have been more than ten years old. He was asking a moderator if he had any other blurbs as good as SockHeight’s. That’s who I care about. The little kid who needs blurbs because his parent or guardian won’t let him read the excessive nonsense and strong repetitive content you and I read on cyclingnews.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m issuing Andrew a Cease &amp;amp; Desist of my own: until such time where he and Trinity Sports Management rightfully refer to SockHeight blurbs appropriately —as “Blurbs”, “Art”, or “Word art— I’m not going to use &lt;em&gt;that Gerro line&lt;/em&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.sockheight.com&quot; title=&quot;SockHeight&quot;&gt;sockheight.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually, I doubt I’d use it even then… some guy called Lance is letting me use his name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SockHeight&quot;&gt;@SockHeight&lt;/a&gt; fine by me&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Lance Armstrong (@lancearmstrong) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lancearmstrong/statuses/474032886773862401&quot;&gt;June 4, 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So SockHeight is now officially…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Launching this July like Lance on L’Alp d’Huez&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    

  </channel> 
</rss>