<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description></description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 15:08:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2014 15:08:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>

    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gerrogate</title>
      <link>//gerrogate.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author></author>
      <guid>//gerrogate</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;6:20 AM. With a brew in-hand I checked my emails before anything else, which was unusual, as that’s a habit I stopped long ago. So why I broke rank this random Wednesday morning I’ll never know. But it’s a decision that stole my day away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“An email from Andrew McQuaid?”, I muttered mid-brew and half-asleep. “Sent at 2:20am? That’s a Euromail”, I said to Unibox, my email-client-of-choice. Despite the dots, and in light of my under-caffeinated state, I wasn’t prepared for the content of this “Mr Simon Gerrans” titled email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“What the fuck? A ‘Cease and Desist’ letter?”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Confused by its vagueness and bemused by its poor punctuation, I read it again, twice. There was no confusing the complaint —it referred to a blurb I wrote just weeks ago— but there was much confusing the claim.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I refer you to […] the line “Sock Height is launching this July like Gerro on a Belgium berg.” This reference to “Gerro” infringes Mr Gerran’s intellectual property.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Wow”, I said, yummying down on my second Scotch Finger of the day, “Are they taking the piss? Because that is not a &lt;em&gt;line&lt;/em&gt;… that is &lt;em&gt;word art&lt;/em&gt;. And if they think I’m just going to sit here and let them call it otherwise, they can goooo…..”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see, I don’t care about Andrew. I was up on some cycling forums today, there was a kid couldn’t have been more than ten years old. He was asking a moderator if he had any other blurbs as good as SockHeight’s. That’s who I care about. The little kid who needs blurbs because his parent or guardian won’t let him read the excessive nonsense and strong repetitive content you and I read on cyclingnews.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m issuing Andrew a Cease and Desist of my own: until such time that he and Trinity Sports Management rightfully refer to SockHeight blurbs as “Blurbs”, “Art”, or “Word art”, I’m not going to use &lt;em&gt;that Gerro line&lt;/em&gt; on sockheight.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually I doubt I’d use it anyway… some guy called Lance is letting me use his name. So now Sock Height is officially…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Launching this July like Lance on L’Alp d’Huez&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SockHeight&quot;&gt;@SockHeight&lt;/a&gt; fine by me&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Lance Armstrong (@lancearmstrong) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/lancearmstrong/statuses/474032886773862401&quot;&gt;June 4, 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;blockquote class=&quot;twitter-tweet&quot; lang=&quot;en&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got a &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?q=%23CeaseAndDesist&amp;amp;src=hash&quot;&gt;#CeaseAndDesist&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/simongerrans&quot;&gt;@simongerrans&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#39; lawyer for using the word &amp;quot;Gerro&amp;quot; on my website. Any legal advice anyone? &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.co/vdITOLSh12&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/vdITOLSh12&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash; Sock Height (@SockHeight) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SockHeight/statuses/473947231582560256&quot;&gt;June 3, 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;script async=&quot;&quot; src=&quot;//platform.twitter.com/widgets.js&quot; charset=&quot;utf-8&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cease and Desist Letter&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gerro-sockheight-cease-and-desist.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    

  </channel> 
</rss>